http://www.fxlinks.com/privacy.html

User:
Password:
Keep me logged in.
Register
|
I forgot my password
Search:
AdvancedSearch
HomeSubmit LinkLatest LinksTop HitsContactRSS
FX LinksFX Links Privacy PolicyFXLinks.com Privacy Policy
FXLinks.com respects your privacy. This statement of our Privacy Policy explains what information we gather from you and how we use that information. We consider the information you have shared with us strictly confidential and will use that information only as specified in this Privacy Policy or to the extent necessary to comply with applicable law.
Information We Gather and How We Use It
We collect certain information from you in order to provide you with the most interesting and useful Web site possible.
We use your IP address to identify you, to gather demographic information that helps us understand how you and our other customers use our Web site, and to administer our Web site.
Our registration form requires you to give us contact information (e.g. name and email address), demographic information (e.g. country). We use your contact information to contact you about our Web site and provide you with information and promotional material from our partners and advertisers.
From time to time we may supplement information that you provide to us with information received from third parties.
Information We May Disclose
We share demographic, profile and other general information about you and our other customers with our advertisers on an aggregate basis. This means that we tell our advertisers general information about the characteristics of our customer base (e.g. geographical).
Our advertisers may ask us to mail or e-mail you promotional information tailored to your interests. We will send you this information on behalf of our advertisers. From time to time we may use third parties (pursuant to a confidentiality agreement) to assist us in e-mail broadcasts and list management. You may opt-out of receiving these mailings as explained below under the heading "Your Options."
We may release your contact and other information to third parties when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) cooperate with state and federal regulatory agency investigations, (iii) enforce the terms of our User Agreement or License Agreement, or (v) protect the rights of FXLinks.com or others.
Cookies
Our Web site uses "cookies" which deposit certain record keeping information in your hard drive. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, keep track of your preferences, deliver content specific to your interests, and for other similar purposes. These cookies can't read other data from your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites or applications.
Our Web site contains display ads sold by us or by outside advertising agencies. These ads may contain cookies which will be deposited in your hard drive if you click on the ads. Information generated from cookies deposited on your hard drive by our advertisers is collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to this information.
Most browsers are set to accept cookies unless you reconfigure your browser to refuse them or to notify you when you have received one. If you do not accept cookies, you will not be able to use certain features of our site.
Subscriptions and Purchases
You may subscribe for a fee to certain services through our Web site. Any financial information we collect will be used solely to bill you for the services and items you have purchased and to ship items to you.
Public Forums
Forums are available to you through our Web site. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited responses. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any of your personal information in a public forum.
Security
Our Web site has certain security measures in place in effort to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our Web site contains links to other sites. Global-View.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. You may wish to review the privacy policies of these sites.
Third Party Advertising  We use some third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here
Third Party Cookies  In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique 'cookie' on your browser.
Your Options
Opting to not receive promotional materials from our advertisers or messages from Global-View.com
You may opt-out during the registration process or after registering by visiting us at http://www.global-view.com and using the contact us link to contact us.
Every e-mail we send to you will provide you with instructions on how to unsubscribe so that you will not receive any future e-mails.
Correct or Update Your Information
You may correct or update any information previously provided to us by visiting us at http:/www.FXLinks.com and using the contact us link to contact us.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact
Web Site Administrator news@fxlinks.com
Additional Information
For general information about Internet privacy issues, you may wish to visit the Web site hosted by the Federal Trade Commission at http://www.ftc.gov/privacy.
We may from time to time revise this Privacy Policy. This statement of our Privacy Policy was last revised on March 31, 2009
Please download or enable Adobe Flash to see CitiFX Pro's currency rates widget.
CitiFX Pro
Forex Chart PointsFX Links - The Forex Directory | Privacy Policy | Disclaimer
